export const questionList = [
    {
        question: "Who played superman in the superman 3 movie from the year 1983?",
        answer: "christopher reeve"
    },
    {
        question: "When was Lego Star Wars: The Complete Saga released?",
        answer: "2007"
    },
    {
        question: "Where was Bram Stoker, the author of the horror novel “Dracula” born?",
        answer: "ireland"
    },
    {
        question: "In the movie BFG: Big Friendly Giant, there is a child named Sofie. How old is she?",
        answer: "8"
    },
    {
        question: "Lucas Learning Ltd. made a Star wars game in 1999. In the title there is a name of a Star wars character. What is the name of this character?",
        answer: "yoda"
    },
    {
        question: "In which city was the summer olympics of 1996 held?",
        answer: "atlanta"
    },
    {
        question: "All the main-line star wars movies are numbered in roman numerals. Considering classical roman numeral rules, how many star wars movies can be made?",
        answer: "3999"
    },
    {
        question: "Several movies have been made based on the stories of Roald Dahl, Including Spielberg’s 'The BFG' from 2016. But before becoming an author, Roald Dahl had a very different job. What was his role during WW2?",
        answer: "spy"
    },
    {
        question: "In 1973, b-movie director Irving Lerner finally got a mainstream breakthrough with his filmatization of the book Tom Sawyer. Three years later he would revolutionize modern filmmaking by starting the trend of rushing out a sequel to a successful horror movie, by directing the low budget sequel to which horror movie?",
        answer: "the omen"
    },
    {
        question: "A famous american sitcom about a family stranded on an island, eventually got an even more bizarre spinoff. Where are the family stranded in the spinoff, which coincidentally also is the name of the show?",
        answer: "gilligan's planet"
    },
    {
        question: "In the 2004 movie 'The Terminal', Tom Hanks is stuck at the JFK Airport. And while Tom Hanks plays a fictional character, he is based on an actual person who was stuck at the Charles de Gaulle airport for 18 years. What is the last name of the person Tom Hanks based on?",
        answer: "nasseri"
    },
    {
        question: "Which spell from the Harry Potter series is used to open locked doors?",
        answer: "alohomora"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of the little girl played by Drew Barrymore in the movie ET?",
        answer: "gertie"
    },
    {
        question: "In Indiana Jones and the temple of Doom, what is the name of the young Chinese boy who joins Jones on his adventure?",
        answer: "short round"
    },
    {
        question: "During WW2, the Allies invaded German-occupied France on the coast of Normandy. The operation is depicted in all it's horror throughout modern media, famously in 'Saving Private Ryan'. What is the name of the beach depicted?",
        answer: "omaha beach"
    },
    {
        question: "During WW2, how many Jewish prisoners did Oskar Schindler rescue from Nazi concentration camps?",
        answer: "1200"
    },
    {
        question: "Who wrote the book Jurassic Park?",
        answer: "michael crichton"
    },
    {
        question: "What role did Julia Roberts play in the movie Hook?",
        answer: "tinkerbell"
    },
    {
        question: "'Keep the change, ya filthy animal!' is a quote from what fictional film?",
        answer: "angels with filthy souls"
    },
    {
        question: "The Triceratops lived around 60 million years ago. And while they produced enormous mounds of manure, as depicted in Jurassic Park, how many teeth did they have?",
        answer: "600"
    },
    {
        question: "During the 60’s and 70’s, a man claiming to be an assistant state attorney general, a hospital physician and a successful pilot rose to fame in the USA. What is his full name?",
        answer: "frank william abagnale jr"
    },
    {
        question: "Tom Cruise tried desperately to escape a cult-like society in the movie Minority Report. In real life however he is famously a member of which cult?",
        answer: "church of scientology"
    },
    {
        question: "In this 2001 movie Haley Joel Osment plays the role of a very special child. The movie has become more relevant due to technological advances in the recent years, and this once so distant future, now doesn’t seem so far away. What is the name of the movie?",
        answer: "a.i."
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Lord Voldemort’s snake in Harry Potter?",
        answer: "nagini"
    },
    {
        question: "Did you pay attention? Are you sure? If so, what is the name we’re looking for?",
        answer: "john williams"
    }
];
